export const questions = [
  {
    category: "movies",
    question: "Where were The Lord of The Rings movies filmed?",
    correctAnswer: "New Zealand",
    otherAnswers: ["Ireland", "Iceland", "Australia"],
  },
  {
    category: "movies",
    question: "Which actor hasn't played The Joker?",
    correctAnswer: "Sean Penn",
    otherAnswers: ["Jack Nicholson", "Mark Hamill", "Jared Leto"],
  },
  {
    category: "movies",
    question: "Which movie is this quote from: 'What's in the box?'",
    correctAnswer: "Se7en",
    otherAnswers: ["Speed", "Reservoir Dogs", "Jurassic Park"],
  },
  {
    category: "movies",
    question: "What is the name of Jeff Goldblum's character in Jurassic Park?",
    correctAnswer: "Dr. Ian Malcolm",
    otherAnswers: ["Dr. Malcolm Stevens", "Dr. Evan Malcolm", "Dr. Michael Ian"],
  },
  {
    category: "movies",
    question: "What is the highest grossing film of all time?",
    correctAnswer: "Avatar",
    otherAnswers: ["Avengers: Endgame", "Titanic", "Star Wars: The Force Awakens"],
  },
  {
    category: "television",
    question: "Which Game of Thrones star was nominated for an Emmy for every single season?",
    correctAnswer: "Peter Dinklage",
    otherAnswers: ["Emilia Clarke", "Kit Harrington", "Maisie Williams"],
  },
  {
    category: "television",
    question: "Which US state does Dexter take place in?",
    correctAnswer: "Florida",
    otherAnswers: ["California", "Texas", "New York"],
  },
  {
    category: "television",
    question: "Which TV series has Bryan Cranston not appeared in?",
    correctAnswer: "Friends",
    otherAnswers: ["Power Rangers", "Breaking Bad", "Seinfeld"],
  },
  {
    category: "television",
    question: "In the series SpongeBob Squarepants, what does Spongebob live in?",
    correctAnswer: "A Pineapple",
    otherAnswers: ["A Submarine", "A Rock", "A Mansion"],
  },
  {
    category: "television",
    question: "Which of these British TV series aired first?",
    correctAnswer: "Blue Peter",
    otherAnswers: ["Doctor Who", "Coronation Street", "Peaky Blinders"],
  },
  {
    category: "videogames",
    question: "In which series do you play as Geralt of Rivia?",
    correctAnswer: "The Witcher",
    otherAnswers: ["Elder Scrolls", "Call of Duty", "Baldur's Gate"],
  },
  {
    category: "videogames",
    question: "In the Super Mario series, Mario and Luigi have adversaries called what?",
    correctAnswer: "Wario and Waluigi",
    otherAnswers: ["Bario and Baluigi", "Dario and Daluigi", "Chas and Dave"],
  },
  {
    category: "videogames",
    question: "Advance, Light, Color, and Pocket are all variants of which system?",
    correctAnswer: "GameBoy",
    otherAnswers: ["DS", "Wii", "PlayStation"],
  },
  {
    category: "videogames",
    question: "Which of these is the oldest company?",
    correctAnswer: "Nintendo",
    otherAnswers: ["SEGA", "Atari", "Xbox"],
  },
  {
    category: "videogames",
    question: "Which series features protaganists John Marston and Arthur Morgan?",
    correctAnswer: "Red Dead Redemption",
    otherAnswers: ["Grand Theft Auto", "Medal of Honor", "Resident Evil"],
  },
  {
    category: "sport",
    question: "What jersey number did Michael Jordan wear for the majority of his career?",
    correctAnswer: "23",
    otherAnswers: ["11", "7", "18"],
  },
  {
    category: "sport",
    question: "Who has won the most olympic medals?",
    correctAnswer: "Michael Phelps",
    otherAnswers: ["Simone Biles", "Usain Bolt", "Chris Hoy"],
  },
  {
    category: "sport",
    question: "Who has scored the most goals in their career?",
    correctAnswer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    otherAnswers: ["Lionel Messi", "Pele", "Will Grigg"],
  },
  {
    category: "sport",
    question: "Which colour is not on the olympic rings?",
    correctAnswer: "Orange",
    otherAnswers: ["Black", "Blue", "Green"],
  },
  {
    category: "sport",
    question: "What does WWE stand for?",
    correctAnswer: "World Wrestling Entertainment",
    otherAnswers: ["World Wrestling Enterprise", "Wide Wrestling Entertainment", "West Wrestling Entertainment"],
  },
  {
    category: "history",
    question: "How many wives did Henry VIII have?",
    correctAnswer: "6",
    otherAnswers: ["8", "4", "5"],
  },
  {
    category: "history",
    question: "What was the first animal to go to space?",
    correctAnswer: "Fruit fly",
    otherAnswers: ["Dog", "Chimpanzee", "Spider"],
  },
  {
    category: "history",
    question: "Who was the first president of the United States?",
    correctAnswer: "George Washington",
    otherAnswers: ["Abraham Lincoln", "Thomas Jefferson", "Franklin D. Roosevelt"],
  },
  {
    category: "history",
    question: "What country did Mary, Queen of Scots grow up?s",
    correctAnswer: "France",
    otherAnswers: ["Scotland", "England", "Spain"],
  },
  {
    category: "history",
    question: "Who was the Greek God of War?",
    correctAnswer: "Ares",
    otherAnswers: ["Zeus", "Kratos", "Hermes"],
  },
  {
    category: "animals",
    question: "What is a group of giraffes known as?",
    correctAnswer: "Tower",
    otherAnswers: ["Herd", "Pack", "Gang"],
  },
  {
    category: "animals",
    question: "Which bird can fly backwards?",
    correctAnswer: "Hummingbird",
    otherAnswers: ["Parrot", "Dove", "Pidgeon"],
  },
  {
    category: "animals",
    question: "Which animal is the closest living relative to the T-Rex?",
    correctAnswer: "Chicken",
    otherAnswers: ["Frog", "Vulture", "Lizard"],
  },
  {
    category: "animals",
    question: "Which animal sleeps the longest at a record 20-22 hours per day?",
    correctAnswer: "Koala",
    otherAnswers: ["Cat", "Fox", "Kangaroo"],
  },
  {
    category: "animals",
    question: "Which animal sleeps the least at two hours a day at average?",
    correctAnswer: "Elephant",
    otherAnswers: ["Gorilla", "Lion", "Chameleon"],
  },
]